so we will uh i will first present what we are going to do
in this meeting then uh
ive i will
also take notes
during this meeting and i
will send you uh a summary
then as usual
we will then look at the evaluation criteria
of the prototype presented by uh our two colleagues that make good work and uh then
we will see the financial aspects and the cost of the product then we will uh evaluate the product and uh
end with the conclusion of this project and see whether it fits with it fulf if it fulfil the requirement
or not mmhmm so d lets start with the cost aspect so so i
look at the aspect discussed last
time that is to say uh to have a standard battery to have a yellow banana shaped uh case with uh a rubber
material around it to be uh to feel spongy and uh also at the different aspect like having a wheel etcetera like a banana mmhmm and the cost ended to be ten point seven euros so which is uh good because we had a price gap of twelve point five euros mmhmm so for the financial aspect its okay we
can uh
we can continue with this product uh as if
and we are now going to see the project evaluation with uh our marketing expert
yeah okay so uh you can have my project in uh yeah just a four yeah you have a presentation participant four yes evaluation okay okay okay so you can go we can
go through okay so i made an evaluation and the the evaluation
criteria is made
according to
the users requirements
and the market
trends we talked about uh during the previous uh meetings so you can go through and okay so uh we have uh six points okay we we talked about
before okay so we we want to have a product fancy look and
feel technologically innovative easy
to use fashion easy to find in a room and robust uh and uh uh i have a scale of uh seven points yeah mmhmm yeah okay so i go through all the uh all the points
here and uh according to what you think about the this project you can uh mm make a one point two point or seven point yeah okay okay and after we ha we have
an an average and uh we see mmhmm okay the okay uh
so
uh fancy look and feel what do you think okay
maybe you can presen
okay f between o one
and seven
maybe hold it so i think its uh
very uh very nice i give it a
i give it
a five what do you
think yeah so its
between one and
seven yeah seven is
the highest uh seven is
the
mmhmm i will give
a six i
will give a a five and you
sorry do you vote uh christine eh do you
also vote no i
just want to see something mmhmm maybe we
all
have to agree on a common yeah well we can very easily uh i think uh and need to as well no
problem need to uh i dont
know if you we ha we have to
put uh one uh f if
its better or uhuh so this is
your one is most i so it will have five
point five average um well we can choose what we want yeah
okay lets say that
seven
is the best or maybe we can
say s seven is the best mm okay so so do note
the grade we have five six for me five five
and what whats your choice oh sorry six uh s you can how much
what how much
would
you give on the fancy aspect
on
the fashionable aspect how
much would you you dont answer to this uh questionnaire oh yes i mm i
dunno mm i think
six its a good uh yeah five point five average wa can
mm okay okay well does it
okay
techne technological aspect i sorry okay so after the technological aspect so we
we said uh we have
uh a new technological uh thing with a wheel yeah we have the wheel uh we also have
the rubber
material which make it
uh like new also i think i
would give a
five its
four
four a four also because except
for the wheel we
dont have so much innovation
yeah the rubber
is uh a four okay d
are we including the voice
are you glu are we including the voice in the
end or not i
i yeah no huh
no okay so
whats your
uh grade no four
four so
we have four four f and five we
can put four
yeah for twenty five yeah
four everyone is okay or four poin four four yeah lets put four
yeah okay doesnt it yeah i think so
very
easy
to use
do you
think its easy to use i
give a seven
i think yeah six i
would give a i
would give a seven as well its
very easy to use mm six
for me also six so six point five six point five kay six six
six point five okay okay is it fashion oh yeah its its f its
fruit
fruit shape seven i would say seven and is
very very nice design
yeah
its fashion because its
a fruit and we say that the yeah seven yeah we can we can put a seven here
yeah yeah seven yeah yeah seven
okay well we hope easy to find uh easy to find in a room i lost my banana i think
you cant miss it yeah yeah okay uh yeah
i think its cool i think
we can
put a six
here we
have the lightning
or the lighting
yeah we have the we
dont sesh especially have the lightning but so its yellow so youll
make
the material
transparent so that it uh lights
up completely or yeah its okay i think its very easy to i would say seven yeah seven its hard to miss it six yeah okay is
it is it
robust yeah its rubber made of rubber i think its m
its uh more rubber
than uh
other remote control uh f
yeah its ru its rubber yeah
yeah the only problem there
might be which know i if its very sensitive they will i dont know yeah okay yeah yeah but it is uh it is surrounded by rubber material yeah so maybe we can put a
six yeah mm six or
five everybody is okay six five six is okay six yeah for
me six yeah
okay yeah yeah s now um so tadada we have to sum up everything twenty
thirteen uh twenty twenty six point
five uh seven thirty two
thirty six thirty thir okay
thats thats okay six six is a good yeah the
be good uh if we say
that seven its uh its the better and when uh s six sit six are good its a good uh p product
i think yeah the top mm okay
so six is a so its a good evaluation i think so
will become eight soon its very promising yeah well its a bit biased we have a good price and uh huh yeah okay good so this
prototype is quite
nice because i saw uh some phones that were banana shaped
uh wireless
phones not mobile
ones
wireless for the house uh quite
big also and they were selling something
like a hundred euros two
hundred euros yeah okay
just a just a phone wireless mmhmm so having this at twenty five euros is uh quite
attractive i think yeah i think the
yeah but
almo also the complexity between a phone and a remote control
is