okay so welcome everyone
so we
are here for the kickoff
meeting
of uh the
process of designing a new remote control so i will first start with a warm welcome opening
stuff then uh we will uh see what will be uh our product and what will be the different step we will have to design it and uh then we will uh discuss if we
have few ideas and we will uh end uh by uh dispatching the different task you will be you will have to fulfil to complete this process so sorry uh just one thing uh you
said
twentyfive minutes
but i have something else to do uh so gotta have another meeting uh soon so maybe you could hurry up a bit its true i have another meeting
so if you could uh yeah you have another
meeting soon so you
have to be quick yeah
for the lawnmower project
okay okay so the the goal is to have a remote control so to have an advantage over our competitors we have to be original we have to be trendy and we have to also try
to be userfriendly so uh the design step will be divided in
three uh main points first it
will be the functional design third is the conceptual design
and then is the desired design so the functional design is to identify the main user needs the
technical function the remote control should fulfil and then we will move to f conceptual design where well specify the different component involved what kind of user interf interface we want and what are the different uh
trend in user interface and stuff like that and then the desired devi design will consist in uh specifically implementing and detailing
the choice weve uh made in the second point so i will now ask you which is very important for the design of a new remote control for to uh each of us to
to draw uh
your favourite animal on the white board what an original idea do
you have
any idea of which animal you want to show us
orangutan okay thats good no no n you should write y the name i think n n you should
if you want to react
uh about this wonderful drawing uh
ill let you uh
comment can i give you the
no but i dont
have to say anything when
im drawing the orangutan its
an abstract drawing of an orangutan okay its an abstract drawing yes i think its nice and original
i dont have a red
colour usually
orangutans have red hair so this is
a very important
but i dont have red pen so yes okay
you
want to draw something christine okay
uh sorry you have to
imagine a
little bit um
this sorry
too uh
of course
your
animal is recorded so its not
lost yes i know is
this uh
ah okay
its pretty wha what is
this strange
beast is it
beautiful is it
a monster do you know its a cat its a cat isnt it i thought
these things did not exist yes yes is it
like that me
ah yeah is it better
ah yeah does have
a name yeah okay its my cat okay
its your cat yeah the name is caramel caramel caramel ahha
yeah okay olivier do
you
want
to okay i go but next time youll do something im sure and
you i think im too short for the cables next time i concentrate im a bit short on
cable okay so what could i draw maybe i can draw like a very simplified cow
i dont know if it looks like a cow like
a what
he looks like a bong okay sorry no
quite squarey scary he also i dunno it it looks more like a donkey in fact i would say mm i i think we will be finished this uh is it for uh for putting a for logos
no okay so i hope that it helps you uh
in the process of designing a remote control thats i is there a matter
for a new remote control
okay lets move on so here
the uh financial objective of our project that
is
to say to to have a production cost lower than twelve point five euros and have a
selling price of twice that price t
in order to target a profe profit of uh fifty
uh million euros yeah if its
trendy original i d fulfil the user needs is it uh a single device remote control or is it a multidevice remote control we have to discuss that point ah this is not defined
at all on yeah you you can suggest points like this ah okay so what what so
we have
to decide for example if it can
control one device or multiple so whats what are your ideas about that maybe i can have the your opinion from the
marketing side well uh do we sell other stuff uh
if if we bundle the remote control with something uh to
sell then it could be a single device otherwise it could
be
programmable one otherwise who would buy a remote control from us okay so if it selled uh by
its own i it
it would rather be for multiple device yeah do you agree mmhmm yeah so maybe it should be for multiple devices and uh do you have
any ideas um of uh design ideas or any
uh uh
technical requirement
we we should uh fulfil i think
we shouldnt
have too many b
for my
part no i couldn i cannot fi think of any requirements right now i think if we dont have so many buttons could be nice few buttons okay and do
you have
it also to be to be lighted in
order to be used in the dark might be a good idea yeah okay and do you have any
um any uh idea of
the trend the trend in domain what it shouldnt it should look like or things like
that something which is not squarey maybe uh not a box mm with rou okay like for okay something like that least fits in your hand yeah okay yeah the basic requirement so fit in your hand yeah only a buck and also it
have i it may be it may be important for the remote control to be uh to to resist to various shocks that can happen if it fall mmhmm waterproof waterproof as well and i think we should have a device sorry maybe it is original because you can uh use it in your uh in your bath whereas the others cant maybe waterproof would be very original
havin having a waterproof remote control
so that the people can uh use it
in their bath mm that could be uh yeah but it is still something uh you have to buy
and that is um not maybe very
yeah mayb b but
maybe we can bulk
it with uh already this plastic thing and uh the waterproof uh stuff as well b it
seems uh so but uh if you dont have an waterproof remote control it means you
can just cover it with some plastic and you can
sort
of f and and thats one of the thats one of the shock i
mean there
are people that have a remote control and they
are
worried that its
going
to break and
they put some
extra plastic around it thats people they actually do it themselves
yeah directly i it will look a bulky in that case yeah yeah maybe we can sell uh all that together so so
plastic protection and
uh and a waterproof box as well that might be
good uh track to follow like as an optional thing optional or selled with it and
i i think we should have
something
most of the time i i lose my remote control we should have s uh special bu button on the tv to
make the remote control
beeping
yeah maybe we can have uh but we dont design the tv ah yeah maybe
we can
have
uh something you whistle and uh the remote
control uh beep yeah barks yeah barks yeah barks
so
we
can uh have a whistle uh remote control yeah yeah whistle i dont know whistleable whistle tracking th whistle tracking yeah whistle tracking remote
control thats a good idea thats very original and thats can uh improve thats thats quite cool but uh of course we you dont normally need uh any audio uh recording stuff on your remote control right yeah d d uh
so i its just going to add t to the cost yeah but s still we have to mm we have to have an advantage over our competitors i think this
is a good advantage its cool i think i like the idea but im not sure about the what you who is giving whos giving whos giving
our budget yeah we have to ask yeah
whos yeah we have to ask the
quest of
thats uh design to the
uh
industrial um
designer yeah yeah
which is you kay yeah okay okay so try to find that for